<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<html>
	
	<homePage>
	
		<home>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">FOLEY</font> - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/home1.jpg</imgPath>
		</home>
		<home>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">RECORDING</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/home2.jpg</imgPath>
		</home>
		<home>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">PRODUCTION </font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/home3.jpg</imgPath>
		</home>
		
	</homePage>
	<studioPage>
		
		<studio>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">CONSOLES</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/studio1.jpg</imgPath>	
		</studio>
		<studio>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">SOFTWARE</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/studio2.jpg</imgPath>	
		</studio>
		<studio>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">OUTBOARD</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/studio3.jpg</imgPath>	
		</studio>
		
	</studioPage>
	<foleyPage>
		
		<foley>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">ADR FOLEY</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/foley1.jpg</imgPath>	
		</foley>
		<foley>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">SOUNDTRACKS</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/foley2.jpg</imgPath>	
		</foley>
		<foley>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">SPECIAL FX</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/foley3.jpg</imgPath>	
		</foley>
		
	</foleyPage>
	<hirePage>
		
		<hire>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">INSTRUMENT HIRE</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/hire1.jpg</imgPath>	
		</hire>
		<hire>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">ROOM HIRE</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/hire2.jpg</imgPath>	
		</hire>
		<hire>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">BACKLINE HIRE</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/hire3.jpg</imgPath>	
		</hire>
		
	</hirePage>
	<clientsPage>
		
		<clients>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">THE DRONES</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/clients1.jpg</imgPath>	
		</clients>
		<clients>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">BERTIE BLACKMAN</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/clients2.jpg</imgPath>	
		</clients>
		<clients>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">NUNN FU</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/clients3.jpg</imgPath>	
		</clients>
		
	</clientsPage>
	<ravesPage>
		
		<raves>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">SPARKADIA</font>  - MVM Studios offer state of the art recording facilities in a relaxed and vibed environment. We can offer a high standard of production in a friendly and relaxed setting close to the beach and all amenities. Atmosphere is abundant in our verdant settings in the Northern Beaches.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/raves1.jpg</imgPath>	
		</raves>
		<raves>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">BERTIE BLACKMAN</font>  - Along with Bertie MVM has serviced Hailer, The Grymm, Angus and Julia Stone, Larrissa McKay, Sundayze, Finis Hominis, The Obvious Fire, Shot, The Orange Bird, The Fumes,  The Camels,  Jet, Youth Group, The Vines, Dragonfly, Aaron Lyon, Brian Campeau, Jeff Stanley,  Jim Pike, Amberdeen and Before The Storm.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/raves2.jpg</imgPath>	
		</raves>
		<raves>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">AND MANY OTHERS</font>  - Sparkadia, Cuthbert and the Nightwalkers, Bertie Blackman, Swimming Underground, Blackwater Fever, The Drones, Sunroom, To The Throne, Tangles, The Mules, The Bellows, Jordan Miller, The Relapse, The Duchesses, Meniscus, The Chaperones, The Mischief, Renny Field, Radiophobia,]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/raves3.jpg</imgPath>	
		</raves>
		
	</ravesPage>
	<staffPage>
		
		<staff>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">JASON MANNELL</font>  - Jason Mannell. Co-owner and engineer. 10 years ProTools experience. 20 years in studios in the U.S. and Australia. Also a freelance Foley and ADR recordist. Musician and Songwriter.]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/staff1.jpg</imgPath>	
		</staff>
		<staff>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">GAVIN LEACH</font>  - Co-owner, engineer, facility coordinator. Also looks after the PA hire department at MVM. Gavin and Jason are also the prorietors of Billy Hydes Northern Beaches and can be found at the shop!]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/staff2.jpg</imgPath>	
		</staff>
		<staff>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">RYAN HAZELL</font>  - Ryan is a junior partner in MVM Studios and has contributed the Amek console and Mac G4 that are some of the driving components in the studio. He has toured extensively with many notable acts including a European Tour as Front of House engineer for The Drones!]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/staff3.jpg</imgPath>	
		</staff>
		
	</staffPage>
	<contactPage>
		
		<contact>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">OUR LOCATION</font>  - MVM Studios is located a short walk away from the beach at Mona vale! You can swim while the rest of the band puts down those difficult takes or stroll around the shops and laze in our lounge!]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/contact1.jpg</imgPath>	
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">CONTACT US</font>  - You can book a session by ringing us on 9986 0589<br><br>Or drop us an email -<br><br>Email: <font color = "#CC9900"><a href="mailto:info@mvmwarehouse.com">info@mvmwarehouse.com</a></font>]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/contact2.jpg</imgPath>	
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<textArea><![CDATA[<font color = "#CC9900">LOCAL FACILITIES</font>  - Mona Vale has a variety of facilities including excellent food and local pubs - we can advise you of many things to while your singer struggles with those difficult takes - and his or her ego!]]></textArea>
			<imgPath>images/contact3.jpg</imgPath>	
		</contact>
		
	</contactPage>
	
</html>